Mobius, Inc. Records MS208
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic materials, 1975 -- 2005; MS208.007; 12.0 Linear Feet
  - Slides, 1975 -- 2004; 1988 -- 2003; MS208.007.002; 9.6 Linear Feet
    - Ends and Beginnings, Judy Dworin, 1992; MS208.007.002.060.00026; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Art Rages 4 Ever, 1992; MS208.007.002.060.00027; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Stirring, Spinning, Sweeping, Marilyn Arsem, Helen Shlien, 1992; MS208.007.002.060.00028; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Two Sand Performances and a Couple Racoons, Ean White, Mari Novotny-Jones, Sarah Hickler, 1992; MS208.007.002.060.00029; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Great Wall of Art, Linda Graetz, 1992; MS208.007.002.060.00030; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Cloister, Frank Vasella, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00031; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Encounters in an Empty Room, Mary Trev Warren, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00032; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - New England Soundscapes: Composer Performing with Computers, Neil Leonard, Richard Boulanger, Ron Kuivilla, Larry Polenski, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00033; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Reflections of Creativity, Raqib Hassan, Ensemble Mogra, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00034; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Psychic Inventory, Behavior Trace, Lewic Gesner, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00035; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Works in Progress #33, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00036; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - It Don't Mean a Thing if You Don't Plug it in Andrew Neumann et al, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00037; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Red in Woods, Marilyn Arsem, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00038; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - It Don't Mean a Thing if You Don't Plug it in, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00039; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Unfolding the Long View, Peter Burns, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00040; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Poor Fish, Ros Barron, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00041; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Red in Woods, Marilyn Arsem, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00042; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Student Works, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00043; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Boston High School Freedom of Expression Project, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00044; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Empty Words: In the Spirit of John Cage, Tom Plsek, Meredith Davis, Larry Johnson, David Miller, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00045; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Movement Works in Progress #3, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00046; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Great Grandmother Project, Margaret Tittemore, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00047; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Stirring, Spinning, Sweeping, Marilyn Arsem, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00048; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - I am German, Gary Duehr with Theatre S, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00049; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Wailing Hot, Ellen Band, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00050; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Glamor Animal Series, Pam Wunderlich, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00051; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Estevanico, Taylor McLean, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00052; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Party Universe, Kathy Chapman, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00053; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - The Long View, Ron Wallace, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00054; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Objects Lie on a Table, David Miller, Steve Thomas, Mary Curtin, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00055; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - My Murderer, Kristin Johnson, True Onion, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00056; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Bringing Homes the Bacon and Other Labors of Love, Nancy Adams, Sarah Kickler, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00057; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Pursuit of the Red Square, Ann Scott, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00058; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - The Radio and the Movie Screen, Ean White, Andrew Neumann, Sarah Hickler, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00059; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Why Can't I be Everywhere, Ellen Anthony, Sue Bhuner, Melanie Braverman, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00060; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - An Act of Resistance: Making Community(ies), Chuck Walsh, Resist Grantees, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00061; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Experimental Music for Brass: Endless Snake and Bare Bones, Tom Plsek, Mark Harvey, Phil Wilson, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00062; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - An Act of Resistance: Making Community(ies) Resist Grantees, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00063; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Open Mouth Series, Charles Coe, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00064; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Two Sound Performances and a Few More Racoons, Ean White, Mari Novotny-Jones, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00065; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Blasphemies and Other Unspeakable Thoughts, Taylor McClean, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00066; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Art Rages - Wrath, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00067; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Memory Portals, Nancy Rider, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00068; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Movement Works in Progress #4, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00069; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Works in Progress #34, 1993; MS208.007.002.060.00070; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Terminal House, Meredith Davis, December 1993, MS208.007.002.060.00071; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Her Dream Stories (to be continued), Judy Dworin and Performance Ensemble, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00072; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Foundry Music, Landon Rose, Michelle Braden, Patricia McMahon, Steve Wilmore, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00073; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Medusa/Myself, Margaret Tittemore, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00074; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Ear Motor, elizabeth Whirlabout, Dane Rosencrantz, Raquib Hassan, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00075; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Frontiers, Crisus, Jeff Becker, Malcolm McClay, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00076; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Student Works #6, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00077; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Outsider Music by the Outsider Ensemble, Tom Plsek, Jon Damian, Mark Harvey, John Voigt, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00078; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Student Works #6, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00079; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Red in Woods, Marilyn Arsem, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00080; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - A Night in Galen, Full Moon Gruel, Tom Jones, Martha Jones, Greta Billinger, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00081; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Boston High School Freedom of Expression Project, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00082; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Here/Not Here, Sarah Hickler, Own Furshpan, Stephanie Cohen et al, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00083; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Waiting for the Dawn and Je t'attends: Facing East, Erica Batdorf, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00084; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Family Values at Wheaton, Meredith Davis, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00085; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Dreams of Forgotten Alchemists (WIP), Mari Novotny-Jones, Cathy Nolan, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00086; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Boston High School Freedom of Expression Project, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00087; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Pigs Feet and Marble Skies, Joseph Wilson, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00088; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Transmography, Nora Valdez, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00089; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Works in Progress #35, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00090; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Amuserama II, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00091; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Under the Red Sun, Taylor McLean, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00092; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Away, End of the Line, James Williams, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00093; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Fly By Night, Movement and Construction, Danny Lepkoft, Nancy Adams, Sarah Hickler, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00094; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Trading Histories, Caroline Bagenal, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00095; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Foreplay and Backlash: A Transphenoidal Hyphesectomy in Three Parts, Susan McDonald-White, 1994; MS208.007.002.060.00096; Raymond, Bob (Box 60)
    - Inventories, 1994 -- 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00001; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Mothers of Time - PR photos, Marilyn Arsem, Mari Novotny-Jones, Sarah Kickler, Joan Gale, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00002; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - The Mobius Strip at Lincoln Center 'Out of Doors Festival' Nancy Adams, Marilyn Arsem, Mari Novotny-Jones, Sarah Hickler, Joseph Wilson, Taylor McLean, Rochelle Fab, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00003; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Mother of Time rehearsal pictures, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00004; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Mother of Time, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00005; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Movement Works in Progress #5, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00006; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - The Man and the Angel, The Body Reveals, Susan Dibble, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00007; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - 15 Moons in Poom, Exiles, Onsight Dance Co., 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00008; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Hard Target Practice, Andrew Neumann, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00009; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Empty Words, Meredith Davis, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00010; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Sampler, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00011; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Outsider Music by the Outsider Quartet, Tom Plsek, Jon Damian, Mark Harvey, John Voigt, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00012; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Art Rages, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00013; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Image lab Observatory, Image lab, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00014; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Permanent Record, Ken Thompson, Ames Hall, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00015; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Works in Progress #36, 1994; MS208.007.002.061.00016; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Black Widow, n.noon.coda, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00017; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Great Wall of Art "The Image of Man", Linda Gretz, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00018; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Society for Hyper-Progressive Solutions, Caleb Brown, David Sullivan, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00019; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Student Works, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00020; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - From the Annals of Art, Malgosia Askanas, Arnold Vance, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00021; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Movement Works in Progress #6, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00022; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - The Constance of Light, Erik Edison, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00023; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - The Berlin Wall / The Iron Curtain between private and public, Mari Novotny-Jones, Milan Kohut, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00024; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Anyplace But Homes, Charles Gross, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00025; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Out of Egypt have I called my son, Taylor McLean, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00026; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Stark Raving Mobius, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00027; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Fontana Mix and other works by John Cage, David Miller, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00028; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Boston Teens Show, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00029; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Works in Progress #37, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00030; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - New/Short Works, Mobius Artists Group, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00031; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Persephone and Hades, Mari Novotny-Jones, David Miller, Marilyn Arsem, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00032; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - St. Pachomius Smells Female Sexual Misconduct Susan Graham, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00033; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia, Marilyn Arsem and Nancy Adams, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00034; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - The Garden's Secret, Meredith Davis, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00035; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Family Values at Dartmouth, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00036; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - The Red Shoes, M. Tittemore, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00037; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Urban Original, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00038; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Movement Work in Progress #7, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00039; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - 5 PSA 4 Cops, T. McLean, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00040; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Holding Up a Mirror; Dunn, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00041; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Art Rages Redux, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00042; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Somnarium, Frank Vasella, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00043; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - 365 Bag Lunches, Laura Evans, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00044; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Twenty Two Chickens and a Parrot, Cathy Nolan, 1995; MS208.007.002.061.00045; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Memories of Mysticism, Susan Baltozer, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00046; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Caitlin Corbett, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00047; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Sleepathon PR, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00048; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Coordinates for an Alignment of a Jigsaw, Sue Rees, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00049; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - No Bias, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00050; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Acoustic Mirage, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00051; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Edge of Meaning, L. Johnson, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00052; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Hieroglyph, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00053; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Student Works, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00054; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Sifting, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00055; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - I Believe that Wings Shall Lift Me High into the Skies, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00056; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Meeting of the Grange, Cathy Nolan, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00057; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Works in Progress #39, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00058; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Sleepathon, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00059; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Subject to my Stress, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00060; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - UFO Project, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00061; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Light Housekeeping, Chorus Angelorum, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00062; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - One Warm Line, Chang, Todd, Vowling, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00063; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Teen Show, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00064; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Exquisite Corpse for One, Sheila Pepe, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00065; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Iskra Dimitrova, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00066; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Nora Stojanovic, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00067; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Zaneta Vangezi, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00068; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Marga Kiselicka Kalajgievska, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00069; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Mirna Arsovska, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00070; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Mari Novotny-Jones, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00071; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Meredith Davis, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00072; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Margaret Tittemore, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00073; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Cathy Nolan, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00074; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Liquor Amnii, Macedonia, Marilyn Arsem, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00075; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Chifte Amam and Skopje, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00076; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia 1st Day, Group at Mala Stanica, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00077; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia lunceon with Unkorskietal, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00078; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia cafe days, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00079; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia, Nerezi, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00080; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia, Matka, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00081; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia, Bigorski, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00082; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia, Statue on way to Bitolax Ohrid, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00083; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia and Austria, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00084; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Palladia, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00085; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Memory Knot, Sharon Dum, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00086; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Gemini, Riskin Twins, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00087; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Mobius Sampler, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00088; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Movement Works in Progress #8, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00089; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Macedonia, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00090; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Not by Bread Alone S. Bergman, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00091; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Prints, Mobius Artists Group Meetings, 1996; MS208.007.002.061.00092; Raymond, Bob (Box 61)
    - Inventories, 1996 -- 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00001; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Art Rages: Quest, 1996; MS208.007.002.062.00002; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Paintings of Ann Corson, 1996; MS208.007.002.062.00003; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Wool Gathering, Jane Duncan Marshing, 1996; MS208.007.002.062.00004; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Democracy Machine, David Franklin, 1996; MS208.007.002.062.00005; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Lacrima N. Coda, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00006; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Meditation, M. Tittemore, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00007; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Pulse, Shawn Dunn at Lime Facotry Gallery, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00008; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - What Comes Around Goes Around, Miller, Speare, Rose, Johnson, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00009; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Berlin Wall, Koholt, Novotny-Jones, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00010; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Of Substance, C. Greenwood, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00011; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Seventh Generation, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00012; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - The Uncertainty of Belief, S. Baltozer, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00013; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Fruit Jam, A. Hardigg, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00014; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Student Works, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00015; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Scorched Skin, Meredith Davis, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00016; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Kombucha World, V. Lecourtois-Mitchell, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00017; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Berlin Wall III, Icoholt, Novotny-Jones, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00018; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Elegy, J. Speare et al, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00019; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mr and Mrs Zone-again, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00020; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Working Class Man, Taylor McLean, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00021; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Chorus Angelorum and Light House Keeping, David Miller, Mari Novotny-Jones, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00022; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Insatiable Appetite to Please, Maureen Albano, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00023; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Eracism, William Pope L., 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00024; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Teen Show 3, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00025; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Liquor Amnii in Providence (1 of 2), 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00026; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Liquor Amnii in Providence (2 of 2), 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00027; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Summer in Situ, Mobius at Decordova, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00028; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Entering the Hut, S. Dunn, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00029; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Inherited Histories, C. Bagenal, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00030; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mobius Sampler, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00031; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Bass Instincts, Plsek et al, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00032; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Working Class Man, T. McClean, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00033; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Zen Dada, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00034; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Art Rages, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00035; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - The Girl Within, M. Tittemore, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00036; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Works in Progress #41, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00037; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Spoken Word, Tim Mason, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00038; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Room of Forgiveness, K. Gilg, 1997 -- 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00039; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - A Hole in My Heart, J. Szabs, 1997; MS208.007.002.062.00040; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Did you hear that?, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00041; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Footsteps of Arepo, L. Johnson, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00042; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Student Works, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00043; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Blood Money, S. Dunn, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00044; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Street Scene Soprano T. Plsek, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00045; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mobius Art Group at ICA, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00046; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Prof. Grublers' Cabinet of Curiousitiees, T. Carruthers, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00047; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Threading the Needle, Meredith Davis, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00048; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Stork, Meg Cottam, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00049; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Stitches in Time, B. Poole, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00050; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Working Class Man, T. McClean at ICA, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00051; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mobius Benefit at Middle East, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00052; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Magnificat, Mobius Artist Group, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00053; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Four Goats and a Virgin, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00054; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Syd Barrett, Arthur Hardigg, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00055; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mobius Artist Group at DeCordova, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00056; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Teens Show, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00057; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Modern Biology, Amy Wilson, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00058; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Standing Waves, Davis, Rice, Novotny-Jones, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00059; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Variation and Silence, Mobius Artists Group, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00060; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Incidents of Light, B. Beams, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00061; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Open Faucet at Mobius, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00062; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Missing Objects, Shumka, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00063; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Quotidian, M. Tittemore, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00064; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Making and Unmaking, M. Wagner, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00065; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Saric-Installation, Silvo, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00066; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Art Rages, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00067; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Under the Wire, B. and N. Garber, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00068; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Works in Progress #42, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00069; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Within, Megan Hirst, 1998; MS208.007.002.062.00070; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Sound of Space, Donna Coppola, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00071; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - A Matchbox, Plum and Orange, Harding-Hicks, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00072; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - When Bulbous Things Bounce, Danielle Tibedo, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00073; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Transitional Status, C. Maxx, Stevens, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00074; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Low Key, Marjorie Morgan, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00075; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - The Word Goes in your Ear, Tim Mason et al, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00076; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mobius at RISD, Meredith Davis, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00077; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mobius at RISD, Naoe Suzuki, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00078; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mobius at RISD, MAG performance, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00079; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - RISD at Mobius, Installations, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00080; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Mouth Opening Mouth Closing, 1994; MS208.007.002.062.00081; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - The Adventurers of Herm, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00082; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Next is I, Naoe Suzuki, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00083; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)
    - Solar Anus, Ron Athey, 1999; MS208.007.002.062.00084; Raymond, Bob (Box 62)